All new students start their Bodwell experienced in boarding.
보드웰의 모든 신입생들은 기숙사에서부터 시작합니다
The Bodwell boarding program provides students with opportunities
기숙사 프로그램은 학생이 생활 스킬을 향상하고
to improve their life skills and become independent young adults.
자율적인 청년이 될 수 있는 기회를 제공합니다
Through carefully designed programming students are prepared to live more independently.
잘 짜여진 프로그램을 통해 학생은 자율적으로 변하게 됩니다
Once students demonstrate self-discipline and maturity in boarding,
학생이 자기 훈련과 성숙함을 어느정도 증명하면
they are invited to apply to graduate from the boarding program
기숙사 프로그램으로부터의 졸업을 신청해서
for the chance to live with an english-speaking Canadian homestay family.
영어를 쓰는 캐네디언 홈스테이 가족과 살 수 있는 기회가 주어집니다
In order to ensure that students are ready for home state we use many different criteria
학생이 홈스테이에서 살 준비가 되도록 학교에서는 여러가지 기준을 설정했습니다
Number one: age. Students should be 16 or older.
첫째는 나이로, 학생이 만 16세 또는 그 이상이여야 합니다
Number two: Length of time in boarding
둘째로는 기숙사에서 산 기간입니다
Students should spend at least two terms in boarding so their life skills can be properly assessed
학생은 최소 두 학기를 기숙사에서 살아야지만 생활 스킬을 평가 받을 수 있습니다
Number three: good academic results
세번째, 좋은 학업 성적입니다
As homestay students, students will need to be more independent in their study habits
홈스테이 학생은 기숙사처럼 튜터나 자습 시간이 없기 때문에
and will not have the tutoring and study hall support that boarding offers.
보다 공부 습관이 잘 들여져 있어야 합니다
We need to make sure that they can plan their study routines on their own
학교는 학생이 스스로 공부할 수 있다는 것을 확신해야 합니다
Number four: Behaviour. Students should not have had any disciplinary issues.
네번째는 태도입니다. 학생은 징계를 받은 적이 없어야 합니다
If they are on behavioral probation or have had recent disciplinary issues They will not be allowed to move to homestay
학교에서 근신 또는 최근 징계 받은 사례가 있다면 홈스테이로 나갈 수 없습니다
Number five: Life skills.
다섯번째, 생활 스킬입니다
Students should have a strong life skill score.
학생은 높은 생활 스킬 점수를 받아야 합니다
This score will allow us to measure student's readiness for independent living
이 점수를 토대로 학생이 자율적인 환경에 준비가 되었는지 평가합니다
The score is shown on the boarding report card that is received by parents regularly.
점수는 기숙사 성적표에 표기되어 부모님께서 주기적으로 볼 수 있습니다
Once all of these factors are considered
이런 모든 사항들을 고려해서
Students will either be accepted or rejected in their request to leave boarding
학생의 기숙사 졸업 후 홈스테이 신청에 대한
and move to a Bodwell homestay.
허가 또는 거부가 결정됩니다
It is important to remember that for safety reasons,
안전을 위해 홈스테이는 특권임을 명시해야 합니다
homestay is a privilege that is earned. Only those that have truly mastered the ability to be independent,
오직 생활 스킬과 공부 습관의 자율성을 갖춘 학생만이
both in their life skills and in their study habits, will be successful in a homestay.
홈스테이에 가서도 성공할 수 있습니다
Through our experience we want to ensure that all students that go to homestay continue to be successful at Bodwell
기숙사 경험을 통해 홈스테이로 나간 모든 학생들은 꾸준히 학교 생활을 잘 할 수 있습니다